True Story - Fake Wine
Sour Grapes is a documentary film directed by Jerry Rothwell.
Controversy erupts when an unassuming young man floods the American wine market with fake vintages valued in the millions, bamboozling
the wine world elite, in this humorous and suspenseful tale of an ingenious con on the eve of the 2008 stock market crash.
Himself, played by Rudy Kurniawan.
Himself, played by Laurent Ponsot.
Himself, played by Bill Koch.
Self, played by Arthur M. Sarkissian.
Sour Grapes is an American crime documentary about
wine fraudster  Rudy Kurniawan.
Filmmakers Jerry Rothwell and Reuben Atlas  debuted the documentary at film
festivals in October 2016 and on Netflix  the following month.
The film explores themes of auction, fraud, wine drinking.
The tone is intense.